Amay Gawas



+91-8788282901



amaygawas07@gmail.com



+91-9168915331



About me

Hello, I am Amay Gawas,21 years old, I've bachelors degree in Computer Science,While completling my studies I have also strived to further expand my skillset which includes Designing, video Editing and marketing.I am a person who doesn't stop until the work has been fully completed or I have got the results which I have expected.I understand the expectation of the customer and try to make their vision a reality.

Experience

3 months Internship

1st August 2020-31st October 2020 At Bloombit Media

7 months Freelancing

December 2020-july 2021

2 months Internship UI/UX design Intern

25th Oct 2022 to 25th Dec 2021 Bluestream software solutions

6 Months UI/UX designer

26th Dec 2022 to 30th June 2022 Bluestream software solutions

Education

Bsc. Computer Science

Skills

- Wireframing
- UI/UX Design
- Prototyping
- Adobe Creative Cloud

Sample work

https://www.behance.net/ameygawas

References

Mr.Llewellyn Dsouza Bluestream SS Mr.Aditya Naik High Resolution Production

Miss. Sasha Dsouza Bluestream SS Miss. Likita Shetty Asst. Professor Govt. college khandola